David Locke Papers MS122
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Agbadza collection, 2011; MS122.003; 250 Digital Object(s)
  - Ahor De Lia Gba Adzigo, 2011; MS122.003.017; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Ahor De Lia Gba Adzigo interview, 2011; MS122.003.017.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor De Lia Gba Adzigo commentary, 2011; MS122.003.017.00010; Locke, David
  - Morxe Nue Bla Gbadza, 2011; MS122.003.018; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Morxe Nue Bla Gbadza audio, 2011; MS122.003.018.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Morxe Nue Bla Gbadza full score, 2011; MS122.003.018.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Morxe Nue Bla Gbadza drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.018.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Morxe Nue Bla Gbadza drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.018.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Morxe Nue Bla Gbadza drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.018.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Morxe Nue Bla Gbadza song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.018.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Morxe Nue Bla Gbadza song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.018.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Morxe Nue Bla Gbadza song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.018.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Morxe Nue Bla Gbadza interview, 2011; MS122.003.018.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Morxe Nue Bla Gbadza commentary, 2011; MS122.003.018.00010; Locke, David
  - Ahor Lem Lo Ahor Le Ma, 2011; MS122.003.019; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Ahor Lem Lo Ahor Le Ma audio, 2011; MS122.003.019.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor Lem Lo Ahor Le Ma full score, 2011; MS122.003.019.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor Lem Lo Ahor Le Ma drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.019.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor Lem Lo Ahor Le Ma drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.019.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor Lem Lo Ahor Le Ma drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.019.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor Lem Lo Ahor Le Ma song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.019.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor Lem Lo Ahor Le Ma song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.019.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor Lem Lo Ahor Le Ma song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.019.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor Lem Lo Ahor Le Ma interview, 2011; MS122.003.019.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ahor Lem Lo Ahor Le Ma commentary, 2011; MS122.003.019.00010; Locke, David
  - Kundoviwo Tsor Ameta De Tu Me Di O, 2011; MS122.003.020; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Kundoviwo Tsor Ameta De Tu Me Di O audio, 2011; MS122.003.020.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kundoviwo Tsor Ameta De Tu Me Di O full score, 2011; MS122.003.020.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kundoviwo Tsor Ameta De Tu Me Di O drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.020.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kundoviwo Tsor Ameta De Tu Me Di O drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.020.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kundoviwo Tsor Ameta De Tu Me Di O drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.020.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kundoviwo Tsor Ameta De Tu Me Di O song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.020.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kundoviwo Tsor Ameta De Tu Me Di O song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.020.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kundoviwo Tsor Ameta De Tu Me Di O song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.020.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kundoviwo Tsor Ameta De Tu Me Di O interview, 2011; MS122.003.020.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kundoviwo Tsor Ameta De Tu Me Di O commentary, 2011; MS122.003.020.00010; Locke, David
  - Dzogbe Nye Nusu Tor, 2011; MS122.003.021; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Dzogbe Nye Nusu Tor audio, 2011; MS122.003.021.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Nye Nusu Tor full score, 2011; MS122.003.021.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Nye Nusu Tor drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.021.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Nye Nusu Tor drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.021.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Nye Nusu Tor drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.021.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Nye Nusu Tor song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.021.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Nye Nusu Tor song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.021.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Nye Nusu Tor song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.021.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Nye Nusu Tor interview, 2011; MS122.003.021.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Dzogbe Nye Nusu Tor commentary, 2011; MS122.003.021.00010; Locke, David
  - Kawo Nue Torvi Norvi Kawo Nue Mado Dzi Do, 2011; MS122.003.022; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Kawo Nue Torvi Norvi Kawo Nue Mado Dzi Do audio, 2011; MS122.003.022.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kawo Nue Torvi Norvi Kawo Nue Mado Dzi Do full score, 2011; MS122.003.022.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kawo Nue Torvi Norvi Kawo Nue Mado Dzi Do drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.022.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kawo Nue Torvi Norvi Kawo Nue Mado Dzi Do drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.022.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kawo Nue Torvi Norvi Kawo Nue Mado Dzi Do drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.022.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kawo Nue Torvi Norvi Kawo Nue Mado Dzi Do song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.022.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kawo Nue Torvi Norvi Kawo Nue Mado Dzi Do song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.022.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kawo Nue Torvi Norvi Kawo Nue Mado Dzi Do song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.022.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kawo Nue Torvi Norvi Kawo Nue Mado Dzi Do interview, 2011; MS122.003.022.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Kawo Nue Torvi Norvi Kawo Nue Mado Dzi Do commentary, 2011; MS122.003.022.00010; Locke, David
  - Ana Wowui Lo He Foawo Fia Ada, 2011; MS122.003.023; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Ana Wowui Lo He Foawo Fia Ada audio, 2011; MS122.003.023.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ana Wowui Lo He Foawo Fia Ada full score, 2011; MS122.003.023.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ana Wowui Lo He Foawo Fia Ada drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.023.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ana Wowui Lo He Foawo Fia Ada drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.023.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ana Wowui Lo He Foawo Fia Ada drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.023.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ana Wowui Lo He Foawo Fia Ada song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.023.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ana Wowui Lo He Foawo Fia Ada song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.023.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ana Wowui Lo He Foawo Fia Ada song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.023.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ana Wowui Lo He Foawo Fia Ada interview, 2011; MS122.003.023.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Ana Wowui Lo He Foawo Fia Ada commentary, 2011; MS122.003.023.00010; Locke, David
  - Amekor Mekorwo Va Anyigba, 2011; MS122.003.024; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Amekor Mekorwo Va Anyigba audio, 2011; MS122.003.024.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Amekor Mekorwo Va Anyigba full score, 2011; MS122.003.024.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Amekor Mekorwo Va Anyigba drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.024.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Amekor Mekorwo Va Anyigba drum langauge A, 2011; MS122.003.024.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Amekor Mekorwo Va Anyigba drum langauge B, 2011; MS122.003.024.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Amekor Mekorwo Va Anyigba song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.024.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Amekor Mekorwo Va Anyigba song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.024.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Amekor Mekorwo Va Anyigba song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.024.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Amekor Mekorwo Va Anyigba interview, 2011; MS122.003.024.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Amekor Mekorwo Va Anyigba commentary, 2011; MS122.003.024.00010; Locke, David
  - Tenge Mado Amede Wenya Gbor, 2011; MS122.003.025; 10 Digital Object(s)
    - Tenge Mado Amede Wenya Gbor audio, 2011; MS122.003.025.00001; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Tenge Mado Amede Wenya Gbor full score, 2011; MS122.003.025.00002; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Tenge Mado Amede Wenya Gbor drum lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.025.00003; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Tenge Mado Amede Wenya Gbor drum language A, 2011; MS122.003.025.00004; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Tenge Mado Amede Wenya Gbor drum language B, 2011; MS122.003.025.00005; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Tenge Mado Amede Wenya Gbor song lead sheet, 2011; MS122.003.025.00006; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Tenge Mado Amede Wenya Gbor song lyrics A, 2011; MS122.003.025.00007; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Tenge Mado Amede Wenya Gbor song lyrics B, 2011; MS122.003.025.00008; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Tenge Mado Amede Wenya Gbor interview, 2011; MS122.003.025.00009; Locke, David; Alorwoyie, Gideon Foli
    - Tenge Mado Amede Wenya Gbor commentary, 2011; MS122.003.025.00010; Locke, David